{'input': 'ATLANTA, Jan. 3, 2018 /PRNewswire/ -- The U.S.-based operations of IDI Gazeley are being renamed IDI Logistics effective with the sale of Gazeley, its European counterpart..IDI Logistics will remain as a portfolio company of Brookfield Asset Management. Brookfield has $265 billion in assets under management, making it one of the largest real estate investors in the world..The new IDI Logistics name retains the trusted IDI brand while reinforcing our commitment to being the leading logistics property company in North America, said Mark Saturno, IDI Logistics Chief Executive Officer. IDI Logistics will continue to provide the same high level of service to its customers and partners in North America under the new brand..Added Saturno, The Gazeley team has been a strong partner for several years and together weve cultivated valuable relationships that undoubtedly made both IDI and Gazeley stronger companies. We wish the Gazeley team well, and congratulate them on the successful sale, which is a testament to their exceptional track record and the strength of Brookfields stewardship..IDI Logistics.IDI Logistics is one of the worlds leading investors and developers of logistics warehouses and distribution parks with 33 million square feet of premier assets under management and additional prime land sites to develop another 20 million square feet of distribution facilities near major markets and transport routes throughout North America. IDI Logistics is a portfolio company of Brookfield Asset Management..For more information, please visit our website at www.idilogistics.com/.View original content with multimedia: http://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/idi-gazeley-becomes-idi-logistics-300577095.html.SOURCE IDI Logistics', 'output': "[['IDI Gazeley', 'ORG', 'Rename', 'IDI Logistics', 'ORG'], ['IDI Logistics', 'ORG', 'Operate_In', 'North America', 'GPE'], ['IDI Logistics', 'ORG', 'Portfolio_Of', 'Brookfield Asset Management', 'ORG/REG'], ['Brookfield Asset Management', 'ORG/REG', 'Has', '$265 billion', 'ECON_INDICATOR'], ['Brookfield Asset Management', 'ORG/REG', 'Is_Member_Of', 'World largest real estate investors', 'CONCEPT'], ['IDI Logistics', 'ORG', 'Retain', 'IDI brand', 'CONCEPT'], ['IDI Logistics', 'ORG', 'Commit', 'Leading logistics property company', 'CONCEPT'], ['IDI Logistics', 'ORG', 'Provide', 'High level of service', 'CONCEPT'], ['IDI Logistics', 'ORG', 'Has', '33 million square feet', 'ECON_INDICATOR'], ['IDI Logistics', 'ORG', 'Has', 'Additional prime land', 'CONCEPT'], ['IDI Logistics', 'ORG', 'Develop', '20 million square feet', 'ECON_INDICATOR'], ['IDI Logistics', 'ORG', 'Near', 'Major markets', 'CONCEPT'], ['IDI Logistics', 'ORG', 'Near', 'Transport routes', 'CONCEPT'], ['IDI Logistics', 'ORG', 'Portfolio_Company_Of', 'Brookfield Asset Management', 'ORG/REG']]", 'category': 'closed_qa'}
{'input': 'TUNIS (Reuters) - Libya’s National Oil Corporation (NOC) said on Wednesday it was investigating the near collision of an unidentified plane with a helicopter carrying staff from a sea platform..The staff from Mellitah Oil and Gas, a joint venture between the NOC and Italy’s Eni, were flying from the Sabratha marine platform to Tripoli when the aircraft converged, “almost ending in tragedy with a direct collision”, NOC said in a statement..It did not give the date of the incident, but said it had been notified by Mellitah on Dec. 31..“Immediately after receiving the news, the National Oil Corporation (NOC) contacted all parties concerned to take urgent steps to investigate the incident and to do what is necessary to ensure that such grave violations are not repeated,” NOC said..Reporting by Aidan Lewis, editing by David Evans. ', 'output': "[['NOC', 'ORG', 'Investigate', 'Incident', 'EVENT'], ['NOC', 'ORG', 'Operate_In', 'Libya', 'GPE'], ['Unidentified Plane', 'COMP', 'Relate_To', 'Incident', 'EVENT'], ['Helicopter', 'COMP', 'Relate_To', 'Incident', 'EVENT'], ['Mellitah Oil and Gas', 'ORG', 'Is_Member_Of', 'NOC', 'ORG'], ['Mellitah Oil and Gas', 'ORG', 'Is_Member_Of', 'Eni', 'COMP'], ['Staff', 'PERSON', 'Participates_In', 'Flight', 'EVENT'], ['Sabratha Marine Platform', 'COMP', 'Operate_In', 'Libya', 'GPE'], ['Tripoli', 'GPE', 'Operate_In', 'Libya', 'GPE'], ['NOC', 'ORG', 'Notify', 'Mellitah', 'ORG'], ['NOC', 'ORG', 'Contact', 'Parties_Concerned', 'ORG'], ['NOC', 'ORG', 'Ensure', 'Violations_Not_Repeated', 'CONCEPT']]", 'category': 'closed_qa'}
{'input': 'January 3, 2018 / 3:25 AM / Updated 8 hours ago PRECIOUS-Gold hits 3-1/2-month highs before dipping on dollar recovery Reuters Staff 4 Min Read .* Technicals show golds rally is overdone in the short-term * Holdings of SPDR Gold Trust fell 0.14 pct on Tuesday * Palladium off record highs hit on Tuesday * Investors await Fed minutes due later on Wednesday (Updates prices) By Sethuraman N R Jan 3 (Reuters) - Gold prices edged down on Wednesday after hitting a 3-1/2-month high, as the dollar recovered from its lows and technical indicators pointed to a short-term correction. Spot gold fell 0.4 percent to $1,312.35 an ounce at 0257 GMT. The precious metal earlier hit $1,321.33, its highest level since Sept. 15. U.S. gold futures were mostly unchanged at $1,315.60 an ounce. Relative strength index shows the metal at overbought levels, which may lead to short term selling, ScotiaMocatta analysts said in a research note. The 14-day relative strength index (RSI) for spot gold touched 75 on Tuesday, it highest since September 2017. An RSI above 70 indicates a commodity is overbought and could lead to a price correction. The dollar index , which measures the greenback against a basket of six major currencies, was up 0.1 percent at 91.964 after falling to a more than three-month low Tuesday. The dollar posted its biggest annual drop since 2003 in 2017, helping gold to an annual increase of more than 13 percent. Bullion surged $55 an ounce in the last three weeks of 2017 alone. Golds medium-term outlook appeared positive, analysts said. At this moment we are expecting some kind of inflationary expectations. People are more optimistic with stock rally are also expecting returns in commodities including gold, said Mark To, head of research at Hong Kongs Wing Fung Financial Group. We should tap the short term opportunities to go long as gold has crossed $1,300 with a momentum. It may act as a support, while $1,340 could be an immediate resistance level and we might reach $1,400 in the first quarter this year. Spot gold may break a resistance at $1,326 per ounce and rise towards the next resistance at $1,380 in three months, according to Reuters technical analyst Wang Tao. Later on Wednesday, investors will turn their attention to the minutes of the Federal Reserves December policy meeting, when it raised interest rates for the third time in 2017. Further cues are likely from U.S. economic data this week, including jobs figures on Friday. Among other precious metals, spot palladium fell 0.1 percent to $1,090.80 an ounce, after hitting a record high on Tuesday at $1,096.50 The metal, which soared 57 percent in 2017, has been surging on fears of short supplies. Analysts expect that about 80 percent of global palladium demand will come from autocatalysts for gasoline-powered cars, which many consumers now prefer over diesel-fuelled vehicles. Spot silver fell 0.8 percent to $17.05 an ounce, after hitting a six-week high at $17.21 earlier in the session. Spot platinum fell 0.8 percent to $936.10 an ounce. (Reporting by Nallur Sethuraman in Bengaluru; editing by Richard Pullin and Subhranshu Sahu)', 'output': "[['Gold', 'CONCEPT', 'Hit', '3-1/2-month highs', 'TIME'], ['Gold', 'CONCEPT', 'Fall', '$1,312.35', 'PRICE'], ['Gold', 'CONCEPT', 'Touch', '$1,321.33', 'PRICE'], ['US gold futures', 'FIN_INSTRUMENT', 'Unchanged', '$1,315.60', 'PRICE'], ['Relative strength index', 'ECON_INDICATOR', 'Show', 'overbought levels', 'CONCEPT'], ['Spot gold', 'CONCEPT', 'Touch', '75', 'ECON_INDICATOR'], ['RSI', 'CONCEPT', 'Above', '70', 'ECON_INDICATOR'], ['Commodity', 'CONCEPT', 'Overbought', 'CONCEPT'], ['Dollar index', 'ECON_INDICATOR', 'Up', '0.1%', 'PRICE'], ['Dollar index', 'ECON_INDICATOR', 'Fall', 'to a more than three-month low', 'TIME'], ['Dollar', 'CONCEPT', 'Posted', 'biggest annual drop', 'EVENT'], ['Gold', 'CONCEPT', 'Annual increase', 'more than 13%', 'PRICE'], ['Gold', 'CONCEPT', 'Surge', '$55 an ounce', 'PRICE'], ['Gold', 'CONCEPT', 'Medium-term outlook', 'Positive', 'CONCEPT'], ['Inflationary expectations', 'CONCEPT', 'Expect', 'CONCEPT'], ['Stock rally', 'CONCEPT', 'Optimistic', 'CONCEPT'], ['Returns', 'CONCEPT', 'Expect', 'in commodities', 'CONCEPT'], ['Gold', 'CONCEPT', 'Cross', '$1,300', 'PRICE'], ['Gold', 'CONCEPT', 'Momentum', 'CONCEPT'], ['$1,340', 'PRICE', 'Could be', 'an immediate resistance level', 'CONCEPT'], ['Gold', 'CONCEPT', 'Reach', '$1,400', 'PRICE'], ['Spot gold', 'CONCEPT', 'Break', 'a resistance at $1,326 per ounce', 'PRICE'], ['Gold', 'CONCEPT', 'Rise', 'towards the next resistance at $1,380', 'PRICE'], ['Federal Reserve', 'ORG/GOV', 'Minutes', 'due later on Wednesday', 'TIME'], ['US economic data', 'CONCEPT', 'This week', 'CONCEPT'], ['Jobs figures', 'CONCEPT', 'On', 'Friday', 'TIME'], ['Palladium', 'CONCEPT', 'Fall', '0.1%', 'PRICE'], ['Palladium', 'CONCEPT', 'Hit', 'a record high', 'TIME'], ['Palladium', 'CONCEPT', 'Soar', '57%', 'PRICE'], ['Palladium', 'CONCEPT', 'Surge', 'on fears of short supplies', 'CONCEPT'], ['Autocatalysts', 'CONCEPT', 'For gasoline-powered cars', 'CONCEPT'], ['Global palladium demand', 'CONCEPT', 'About 80%', 'CONCEPT'], ['Palladium demand', 'CONCEPT', 'Come from autocatalysts', 'CONCEPT'], ['Spot palladium', 'CONCEPT', 'Fall', '$1,090.80', 'PRICE'], ['Spot silver', 'CONCEPT', 'Fall', '0.8%', 'PRICE'], ['Spot silver', 'CONCEPT', 'Hit', 'a six-week high', 'TIME'], ['Spot platinum', 'CONCEPT', 'Fall', '0.8%', 'PRICE']]", 'category': 'closed_qa'}
{'input': 'WASHINGTON (Reuters) - Forty-nine states and the District of Columbia have reached a $45 million settlement with mortgage lender PHH Mortgage Corporation ( PHH.N ) over “alleged misconduct” tied to its servicing single-family mortgages..The settlement resolves allegations that the lender mistreated borrowers from 2009 to 2012, including failing to apply payments promptly, charging unauthorized fees, and threatening foreclosure to borrowers engaged in loss mitigation..The company did not admit to wrongdoing as part of the settlement..Reporting by Pete SchroederEditing by Chizu Nomiyama. ', 'output': "[['WASHINGTON', 'GPE', 'Report', 'PHH Mortgage Corporation', 'COMP'], ['PHH Mortgage Corporation', 'COMP', 'Has', 'alleged misconduct', 'CONCEPT'], ['PHH Mortgage Corporation', 'COMP', 'Settle', ' $45 million', 'ECON_INDICATOR'], ['PHH Mortgage Corporation', 'COMP', 'Operate_In', 'Mortgage Lending', 'SECTOR'], ['PHH Mortgage Corporation', 'COMP', 'Mistreat', 'Borrowers', 'PERSON'], ['PHH Mortgage Corporation', 'COMP', 'Fail', 'Apply payments promptly', 'CONCEPT'], ['PHH Mortgage Corporation', 'COMP', 'Charge', 'unauthorized fees', 'CONCEPT'], ['PHH Mortgage Corporation', 'COMP', 'Threaten', 'Foreclosure', 'CONCEPT'], ['Borrowers', 'PERSON', 'Participates_In', 'Loss mitigation', 'CONCEPT'], ['PHH Mortgage Corporation', 'COMP', 'Not', 'Admit', 'CONCEPT'], ['Pete Schroeder', 'PERSON', 'Reporting', 'Reuters', 'ORG'], ['Chizu Nomiyama', 'PERSON', 'Editing', 'Reuters', 'ORG']]", 'category': 'closed_qa'}
{'input': ' 12 AM / in 3 minutes BRIEF-Franklin Resources Says Ceo Gregory Johnsons Total Compensation For 2017 was $9.9 Million Reuters Staff 1 Min Read .Jan 3 (Reuters) - Franklin Resources Inc: .* FRANKLIN RESOURCES SAYS CEO GREGORY JOHNSONS TOTAL COMPENSATION FOR 2017 WAS $9.9 MILLION VERSUS $12.1 MILLION IN 2016 - SEC FILING Source text: ( bit.ly/2lL6cNi ) Further company coverage:', 'output': "[['Franklin Resources', 'ORG', 'Control', 'Gregory Johnson', 'PERSON'], ['Gregory Johnson', 'PERSON', 'Raise', '$9.9 Million', 'ECON_INDICATOR', '2017', 'GPE'], ['Gregory Johnson', 'PERSON', 'Decrease', '$12.1 Million', 'ECON_INDICATOR', '2016', 'GPE']]", 'category': 'closed_qa'}
{'input': 'Markets on launch pad after Rocket Man boost 1:37pm GMT - 01:29 .European markets start the first trading day of the year on a nervous footing despite record manufacturing surveys for the euro zone. But as Ivor Bennett reports, Asian shares scaled a decade peak after a surprisingly upbeat survey of Chinese manufacturing and signs of a thaw in Korean relations.   .European markets start the first trading day of the year on a nervous footing despite record manufacturing surveys for the euro zone. But as Ivor Bennett reports, Asian shares scaled a decade peak after a surprisingly upbeat survey of Chinese manufacturing and signs of a thaw in Korean relations.  //reut.rs/2A67APu', 'output': "[['European markets', 'GPE', 'Start', 'First trading day of the year', 'EVENT'], ['European markets', 'GPE', 'Operate_In', 'Euro zone', 'GPE'], ['Euro zone', 'GPE', 'Has', 'Record manufacturing surveys', 'EVENT'], ['Asian shares', 'GPE', 'Scale', 'Decade peak', 'EVENT'], ['Asian shares', 'GPE', 'Operate_In', 'Asian market', 'GPE'], ['China', 'GPE', 'Has', 'Upbeat survey of manufacturing', 'EVENT'], ['Korea', 'GPE', 'Has', 'Signs of a thaw in relations', 'EVENT']]", 'category': 'closed_qa'}
{'input': 'January 2, 2018 / 11:40 PM / Updated 6 hours ago U.S. threatens to withhold aid cash to Palestinians Rodrigo Campos 3 Min Read .UNITED NATIONS (Reuters) - U.S. President Donald Trump said in tweets on Tuesday that the United States may withhold future aid payments to Palestinians, accusing them of being “no longer willing to talk peace” with Israel. FILE PHOTO - U.S. President Donald Trump speaks during an address from the White House in Washington, U.S., December 6, 2017. REUTERS/Kevin Lamarque/File Picture .Trump said that Washington gives Palestinians “HUNDRED OF MILLIONS OF DOLLARS a year and get no appreciation or respect. They don’t even want to negotiate a long overdue peace treaty with Israel ... with the Palestinians no longer willing to talk peace, why should we make any of these massive future payments to them?” .The President’s tweets follow plans disclosed by his U.N. ambassador earlier on Tuesday to stop funding a United Nations agency that provides humanitarian aid to Palestinian refugees. .“The President has basically said he doesn’t want to give any additional funding, or stop funding, until the Palestinians agree to come back to the negotiation table,” Ambassador Nikki Haley told reporters when asked about future U.S. funding for the U.N. Relief and Works Agency for Palestinian refugees. .The U.S. is the largest donor to the agency, with a pledge of nearly $370 million as of 2016, according to UNRWA’s website. .Relations between the Palestinians and Washington soured early last month after Trump recognised Jerusalem as Israel’s capital, generating outrage across the Arab world and concern among Washington’s Western allies. .Weeks later, more than 120 countries defied Trump and voted in favour of a U.N. General Assembly resolution calling for the United States to drop its stance on Jerusalem’s status. .“What we saw with the resolution was not helpful to the situation,” Haley said on Tuesday. .“The Palestinians now have to show to the world that they want to come to the table. As of now, they’re not coming to the table but they asked for aid. We’re not giving the aid, we’re going to make sure that they come to the table and we want to move forward with the peace process,” she said. .Palestinian President Mahmoud Abbas has called the Trump administration’s decision on Jerusalem the “greatest crime” and a flagrant violation of international law, and said it was unacceptable for the United States to have a role in the Middle East peace process because it was biased in favour of Israel. .On Tuesday, the Israeli Parliament passed an amendment that would make it harder for it to cede control over parts of Jerusalem in any peace deal with the Palestinians. Reporting by Rodrigo Campos, additional reporting by Eric Beech in Washington D.C., Editing by Rosalba OBrien', 'output': "[['U.S.', 'ORG/GOV', 'Threaten', 'Aid Cash', 'FIN_INSTRUMENT'], ['U.S.', 'ORG/GOV', 'Operate_In', 'United Nations', 'ORG'], ['U.S.', 'ORG/GOV', 'Withhold', 'Aid Payments', 'FIN_INSTRUMENT'], ['U.S.', 'ORG/GOV', 'Accuse', 'Palestinians', 'PERSON'], ['Palestinians', 'PERSON', 'Not_Willing_To', 'Talk Peace', 'CONCEPT'], ['U.S.', 'ORG/GOV', 'Give', 'Palestinians', 'PERSON'], ['Palestinians', 'PERSON', 'Get', 'No_Appreciation', 'CONCEPT'], ['Palestinians', 'PERSON', 'Get', 'No_Respect', 'CONCEPT'], ['U.S.', 'ORG/GOV', 'Plan', 'Stop Funding', 'FIN_INSTRUMENT'], ['U.N.', 'ORG', 'Provide', 'Humanitarian Aid', 'FIN_INSTRUMENT'], ['U.N.', 'ORG', 'Relief and Works Agency', 'Assist', 'PERSON'], ['U.S.', 'ORG/GOV', 'Largest Donor', 'Agency', 'ORG'], ['U.S.', 'ORG/GOV', 'Recognize', 'Jerusalem', 'GPE'], ['Arab World', 'GPE', 'Outrage', 'Trump Decision', 'CONCEPT'], ['U.S.', 'ORG/GOV', 'Western Allies', 'Concern', 'CONCEPT'], ['U.N.', 'ORG', 'General Assembly', 'Vote', 'EVENT'], ['U.N.', 'ORG', 'Resolution', 'Call', 'EVENT'], ['U.S.', 'ORG/GOV', 'Drop', 'Stance', 'CONCEPT'], ['Palestinians', 'PERSON', 'Show', 'World', 'GPE'], ['Palestinians', 'PERSON', 'Want', 'Come_To_Table', 'CONCEPT'], ['U.S.', 'ORG/GOV', 'Make_Sure', 'Move_Forward', 'CONCEPT'], ['Palestinians', 'PERSON', 'Ask', 'Aid', 'FIN_INSTRUMENT'], ['U.S.', 'ORG/GOV', 'Not_Giving', 'Aid', 'FIN_INSTRUMENT'], ['Palestinians', 'PERSON', 'Come_To_Table', 'Table', 'CONCEPT'], ['Peace_Process', 'CONCEPT', 'Move_Forward', 'CONCEPT'], ['Trump', 'PERSON', 'Recognize', 'Jerusalem', 'GPE'], ['Palestinians', 'PERSON', 'Call', 'Crime', 'CONCEPT'], ['Trump', 'PERSON', 'Flagrant_Violation', 'International_Law', 'CONCEPT'], ['Palestinians', 'PERSON', 'Unacceptable', 'Role', 'CONCEPT'], ['U.S.', 'ORG/GOV', 'Biased', 'Favor', 'PERSON'], ['Israel', 'GPE', 'Favor', 'Peace_Deal', 'CONCEPT'], ['Israel', 'GPE', 'Pass', 'Amendment', 'CONCEPT'], ['Israel', 'GPE', 'Control', 'Parts_Jerusalem', 'GPE'], ['Israel', 'GPE', 'Cede', 'Peace_Deal', 'CONCEPT']]", 'category': 'closed_qa'}
{'input': 'January 2, 2018 / 9:44 PM / in 15 hours New U.S. tax law could impact paychecks by February Beth Pinsker 4 Min Read .NEW YORK (Reuters) - The first paychecks of 2018 will be dispatched soon, but it may be weeks or months before taxpayers and payroll processors know how the new U.S. tax laws will affect your take-home pay. .The Internal Revenue Service said it expected to issue guidance in January on how much in taxes employers should withhold based on the new tax rates. Employers and payroll services would then implement those changes starting in February. .You might not even notice when it happens because the effect on your paycheck could be relatively small, depending on your income and your tax situation. .“When the taxes are reduced by 1 to 3 percent, that’s not going to be a huge noticeable difference. It’s not going to be hundreds of dollars,” said Pete Isberg, vice president of government relations at ADP, the largest payroll processor in the United States, servicing the paychecks of one out of every six workers. .A difference of $1,000, for instance, would be less than $40 a pop for a worker paid biweekly. .Your paycheck is not actually a clear indicator of whether your overall taxes have gone up or down because of the new tax law. There may be other factors in your tax situation - such as owning a property or having multiple children - that could affect how much you owe Uncle Sam at the end of the year. .Be prepared for tax uncertainty until you do your taxes for 2018 a year or so from now. You cannot even estimate your taxes until tax professionals and do-it-yourself services like TurboTax update their software. And that cannot happen until the IRS releases the new withholding tables and issues more guidance on the specifics of other tax changes. .“We will be ready to help our customers. We just need more information,” said David Williams, executive director of the Intuit Tax and Financial Center. WAITING FOR W-4 FORMS .You may be tempted to get a jump on the IRS and change how much tax is taken out of your paycheck by adjusting your W-4 form, but that may be premature, warned Isberg. .The IRS said in its last note that it would be attempting to work with existing W-4 forms for now. .The standard federal W-4, which all employees fill out, is based on the notion of “allowances,” which you could adjust based on your personal situation. .In the past, a single person with three children and a home in a high-tax state like New York might have listed themselves as married and claim one allowance per person, plus a few extra because they were likely to itemize their deductions and owe less. A married person with a freelance spouse who owes quarterly taxes might have listed themselves as single to have enough taken out to cover both of them. .The goal of people adjusting their withholding was to come as close as possible to paying the correct amount of tax - rather than owing money at the end of the year or ending up with a giant refund. .But it will all be different math for 2018. .“For first few weeks of January stay put, and see what the IRS comes out with,” said Isberg, who also cautioned that employees should keep an eye on tax changes at the state level. .Above all, do not panic, said Farsheed Ferdowsi, president and CEO of Inova Payroll, which handles paychecks for more than 3,000 companies. .“When you have changes in taxes, it usually goes a lot smoother than most people know,” Ferdowsi said. “If the first (paycheck) is wrong, it catches up on the next one.” Editing by Lauren Young and Lisa Shumaker', 'output': "[['New U.S. tax law', 'EVENT', 'Impact', 'Paychecks', 'COMP'], ['New U.S. tax law', 'EVENT', 'Relate_To', 'Taxpayers', 'PERSON'], ['New U.S. tax law', 'EVENT', 'Relate_To', 'Payroll Processors', 'COMP'], ['Internal Revenue Service', 'ORG/GOV', 'Announce', 'Guidance', 'EVENT'], ['Employers', 'COMP', 'Implement', 'Changes', 'EVENT'], ['Employers', 'COMP', 'Operate_In', 'February', 'GPE'], ['Paychecks', 'COMP', 'Has', 'Small Effect', 'CONCEPT'], ['Paychecks', 'COMP', 'Relate_To', 'Take-home Pay', 'CONCEPT'], ['Paychecks', 'COMP', 'Relate_To', 'Income', 'CONCEPT'], ['Paychecks', 'COMP', 'Relate_To', 'Tax Situation', 'CONCEPT'], ['Taxpayers', 'PERSON', 'Prepare', 'Tax Uncertainty', 'CONCEPT'], ['IRS', 'ORG/GOV', 'Release', 'New Withholding Tables', 'PRODUCT'], ['IRS', 'ORG/GOV', 'Issue', 'More Guidance', 'EVENT'], ['Employees', 'PERSON', 'Need', 'More Information', 'CONCEPT'], ['Employees', 'PERSON', 'Adjust', 'W-4 Forms', 'PRODUCT'], ['IRS', 'ORG/GOV', 'Work', 'Existing W-4 Forms', 'PRODUCT'], ['Standard Federal W-4', 'PRODUCT', 'Based_On', 'Allowances', 'CONCEPT'], ['Employees', 'PERSON', 'Adjust', 'Allowances', 'CONCEPT'], ['Employees', 'PERSON', 'Come', 'Close', 'CONCEPT', 'Paying', 'CONCEPT', 'Correct', 'CONCEPT', 'Amount', 'CONCEPT', 'Tax', 'CONCEPT'], ['Employees', 'PERSON', 'Owe', 'Money', 'CONCEPT', 'End_Of', 'CONCEPT', 'Year', 'GPE'], ['Employees', 'PERSON', 'End_Up', 'Giant Refund', 'CONCEPT'], ['IRS', 'ORG/GOV', 'Update', 'Software', 'PRODUCT'], ['Tax Professionals', 'PERSON', 'Update', 'Their Software', 'PRODUCT'], ['Do-it-yourself Services', 'COMP', 'Like TurboTax', 'PRODUCT', 'Update', 'Their Software', 'PRODUCT'], ['Employees', 'PERSON', 'Adjust', 'W-4 Forms', 'PRODUCT'], ['Employees', 'PERSON', 'Premature', 'Warned', 'Isberg', 'PERSON'], ['IRS', 'ORG/GOV', 'Work', 'Existing W-4 Forms', 'PRODUCT'], ['Employees', 'PERSON', 'Stay', 'Put', 'CONCEPT'], ['Employees', 'PERSON', 'See', 'What', 'PRON', 'Comes', 'Out', 'WITH', 'PRON'], ['Employees', 'PERSON', 'Keep', 'Eye', 'On', 'Tax Changes', 'EVENT', 'At', 'CONCEPT', 'State', 'GPE', 'Level'], ['People', 'PERSON', 'Do', 'Not', 'Panic', 'CONCEPT'], ['Changes', 'CONCEPT', 'Taxes', 'CONCEPT', 'Usually', 'CONCEPT', 'Go', 'CONCEPT', 'Smoother', 'CONCEPT', 'Most', 'CONCEPT', 'People', 'PERSON', 'Know', 'CONCEPT'], ['First', 'CONCEPT', 'Pay', 'CONCEPT', 'Wrong', 'CONCEPT', 'Catches', 'CONCEPT', 'Up', 'CONCEPT', 'Next', 'CONCEPT', 'One', 'CONCEPT']]", 'category': 'closed_qa'}
{'input': 'Published: Dec 7, 2017 4:58 a.m. ET Share .Collectors and Hollywood buyers are snapping them up OldPhoneWorks.com This chrome-plated Western Electric 302 model from the 1930s sells for $449.95 at Old Phone Works. .By Bonnie Miller Rubin .When Don Woodbury opened a cellphone store in 2001, he included a few old phones as part of the décor, reflecting the historic district where the business was located. .Soon customers were asking to purchase the vintage models. “They’d just come up to me and say, ‘I want one of those.’ It didn’t take me long to realize that there was a good internet market for this stuff,” Woodbury says. .Some 16 years later, Oldphoneworks.com , based in Kingston, Ontario, has grown to become one of the biggest sellers of antique phones, whether it’s the “candlestick” style familiar from old films and TV shows or the clunky desk models that were fixtures at grandma’s house. .Woodbury’s base is a small but loyal group of collectors with a taste for nostalgia, along with a handful of people looking to buy old models in bulk, such as movie producers trying to conjure up the past and hotel moguls looking to add a touch of uniqueness to rooms. .“It’s kind of amazing that we’ve been able to create a viable business from repurposing and redeploying obsolete technology that would otherwise end up in the trash,” says the 59-year-old Woodbury, who sold his 50-store cellphone chain in 2013. .Many small companies have done very well by selling niche products that have long since been put out to pasture, whether it’s vinyl records, typewriters or anything else that captures people’s fancy. .Also read: Old technology that’s worth bringing back—and not for the nostalgia .For some entrepreneurs, vintage sales are a sideline. Dr. Jonathan Finder started Oldphones.com 16 years ago when he was a young physician, and the second income helped him pay off student loans. .Now his job as a pediatric lung specialist keeps him from putting in the time to acquire new customers. And a downturn in landline sales has hurt business. .But he keeps at it, in no small part because he’s an unabashed fan of the craftsmanship and history of his merchandise. “How many electromechanical objects that are 50 to 70 years old do exactly what they did when they were first made?” Finder says. “The phones of the ’30s and ’40s outclass anything on the market today.” A new calling .For other entrepreneurs, like Woodbury, retro devices are their sole focus. The market for these phones would seem pretty small to build a business on. Two groups—the Antique Telephone Collectors Association and Telephone Collectors International—have only 1,125 members total. .Don’t miss: This is the vintage technology some companies are using to store your data .Yet buyers have been eager enough not only to keep Woodbury’s operation afloat but allow it to thrive, even enough to support a four-person staff. Revenue, he says, can hit 50,000 Canadian dollars (roughly US$39,000) in a good month, and though he doesn’t track long-term growth, he says that sales have shown a consistent year-to-year increase since the beginning. .When original equipment is unavailable, the company uses reproduction parts—such as cloth-covered cords—manufactured in its own workshop. Additionally, Oldphoneworks.com has the capability to repair and refurbish models that aren’t in its inventory, a service that accounts for about 10% of the company’s revenue. .Woodbury’s customers are both “repeat buyers; people who are going through their collection and want to upgrade, so they’ll come to us to order the one part they need,” he says, and “a lot of one-offs, where someone Googles us because they need parts.” .Typically, Woodbury gets his inventory from individuals or estates looking to liquidate their collections. His average telephone sale is $250, a healthy return on his average investment of $50, not counting the cost of labor for refurbishing. Prices usually range from $100 to as much as $8,000 for a rare model, such as the 1905 Strowger Candlestick, the first commercially available dial telephone. .(A Kansas City undertaker, Almon Strowger, believed that the only local operator was steering business calls to his competitor, who also happened to be her husband. So he invented dial service, bypassing operator intervention.) OldPhoneWorks.com Hello! This Strowger Candlestick dial phone goes for $7,999. .“A phone like that may sit there for five years, but eventually someone will buy it,” Woodbury says. “If people really want something, they’re willing to pay for it. You just have to be patient.” .To build consumer trust, he offers a one-year, repair-or-replace warranty—which gives him an edge over garage sales and flea markets, where the mantra is “Let the buyer beware.” He also says he can offer items in bulk, which is difficult for other dealers. A trunk line .The company doesn’t do much marketing. Mostly it involves making sure customers can find 20th-century technology using 21st-century methods. General manager Matt Jennings, 31, makes updating social media a top priority, trying to land the company at the top of Google rankings in their category. .When he answered a help-wanted ad two years ago, he didn’t know a spit-cup receiver from an F1 handset. “I thought I’d be repairing cellphones. I certainly didn’t think this would be much of a market,” he says. “After my first day, I realized I was wrong.” .Beth Howe, like many buyers, found her way to Oldphoneworks by googling. She isn’t a collector, but lusted after a Western Electric 500—the phone of her childhood—for her Topanga, Calif., home. .“I have fond memories of avocado-green kitchen appliances,” Ms. Howe says. “Maybe it’s just reaching adulthood that has made me nostalgic for the late ’60s, early ’70s design sensibility.” .An online search brought her to the site, and she fell hard for a dark red Western Electric 302 instead. Last produced in 1954, the phone’s sleek lines and distinctive chime made the model a staple of Hollywood’s Golden Age. .“I thought, what fun to have a phone, not from my own childhood era, but from that classic period,” says Ms. Howe, a visual-effects production supervisor, who worked on the recently released film “Blade Runner 2049.” .“I was especially enamored of the matching textile cord…and the clickety, clickety, clack of the dialing mechanism and the ringer, which is as good as a time machine to transport me back,” she says. .You might like: How to value the stuff you inherited A starring role .Other regular clients are the TV and movie industries, which account for 15% of the firm’s revenue. .“It’s just been building on its own,” Woodbury says. Recently, he says, “we got calls from two different production companies on the same day asking us to rush phones that they need on the set.” .Jess Royal, set decorator for the Netflix NFLX, -0.39% series “Stranger Things,” calls the company her “go-to source.” .“It’s super hard to find a whole bunch of phones in working condition, such as ones that all light up for a police station scene,” she says. “They’ve been great for us.” .Also read: 5 strange things about ‘Stranger Things’ season 2 .When a certain style Woodbury has supplied appears on the screen, his staff will see an immediate blip in sales. .“We won’t sell any red pay phones for ages, then, all of a sudden, we’ll sell four in a day,” he says. .A big order came in recently from', 'output': "[['Don Woodbury', 'PERSON', 'Operate_In', 'Oldphoneworks.com', 'ORG'], ['Oldphoneworks.com', 'ORG', 'Sell', 'Antique Phones', 'PRODUCT'], ['Customers', 'PERSON', 'Buy', 'Antique Phones', 'PRODUCT'], ['Don Woodbury', 'PERSON', 'Sold', '50-store cellphone chain', 'ORG'], ['Small Companies', 'ORG', 'Do_Well_By', 'Selling', 'Operate_In', 'Niche Products', 'PRODUCT'], ['Dr. Jonathan Finder', 'PERSON', 'Start', 'Oldphones.com', 'ORG'], ['Dr. Jonathan Finder', 'PERSON', 'Keep', 'At_It', 'Operate_In', 'Oldphones.com', 'ORG'], ['Entrepreneurs', 'PERSON', 'Sell', 'Vintage Sales', 'PRODUCT', 'As_A_Sideline', 'SECTOR'], ['Oldphones.com', 'ORG', 'Has', 'One_Four-Person_Staff', 'PERSON'], ['Oldphoneworks.com', 'ORG', 'Revenue', '50,000 Canadian Dollars', 'ECON_INDICATOR', 'In_A_Good_Month', 'TIME'], ['Oldphoneworks.com', 'ORG', 'Repair_And_Refurbish', 'Models', 'PRODUCT'], ['Customers', 'PERSON', 'Come', 'To_Order_Parts', 'PRODUCT'], ['Typically', 'Adv', 'Woodbury', 'Gets', 'Inventory', 'PRODUCT', 'From', 'Individuals_Or_Estates', 'PERSON'], ['OldPhoneWorks.com', 'ORG', 'Offer', 'One-Year_Warranty', 'SERVICE'], ['Beth Howe', 'PERSON', 'Buy', 'Western Electric 302', 'PRODUCT'], ['TV_And_Movie_Industries', 'ORG', 'Account_For', '15%', 'ECON_INDICATOR', 'Of_The_Firm_s_Revenue', 'SECTOR'], ['Jess Royal', 'PERSON', 'Call', 'Oldphoneworks.com', 'ORG', 'Her', 'Go-to_Source', 'SERVICE'], ['Woodbury_s_Staff', 'PERSON', 'See', 'Blip_In_Sales', 'ECON_INDICATOR', 'When', 'A_Certain_Style', 'PRODUCT', 'Appears', 'On_The_Screen', 'EVENT']]", 'category': 'closed_qa'}
{'input': 'Trump says sanctions are having an effect on North Korea 11 mins ago Facebook .On Tuesday, Seoul proposed holding talks with North Korea near their shared border next week. .Through sanctions, the United Nations has aimed to limit the supply of oil going to North Korea in an effort to curb its nuclear and missile programs. In recent days, South Korea has said it has seized two ships suspected of transferring oil to the regime in violation of sanctions . .Last week, Trump sent a warning to China following reports that Beijing allowed oil to go into North Korea. China has denied illegally providing oil. .Reuters separately reported that Russian tankers supplied oil to North Korea , though there is no evidence yet that the Russian state backed the shipments, according to the wire service. .It is unclear if the ships seized by South Korea are linked to the alleged Chinese and Russian transactions. ', 'output': "[['Trump', 'PERSON', 'Says', 'Sanctions', 'ORG/REG'], ['United Nations', 'ORG/REG', 'Has', 'Limit', 'NounSupply', 'Oil', 'ORG', 'North Korea', 'GPE'], ['North Korea', 'GPE', 'Has', 'Nuclear', 'AND', 'Missile', 'Programs', 'Noun'], ['South Korea', 'GPE', 'Has', 'Seized', 'Two', 'Ships', 'Noun'], ['Ships', 'Noun', 'Suspected', 'Transferring', 'Oil', 'Noun', 'North Korea', 'GPE', 'Violation', 'ORG/REG', 'Sanctions'], ['Trump', 'PERSON', 'Sent', 'Warning', 'China', 'GPE', 'Following', 'Reports', 'Beijing', 'Allowed', 'Oil', 'Noun', 'North Korea'], ['China', 'GPE', 'Denied', 'Illegally', 'Providing', 'Oil', 'Noun'], ['Reuters', 'ORG', 'Reported', 'Russian', 'Tankers', 'Supplied', 'Oil', 'Noun', 'North Korea'], ['No', 'Determiner', 'Evidence', 'Noun', 'Russian', 'State', 'Backed', 'Shipments', 'Noun'], ['It', 'Pronoun', 'Unclear', 'If', 'Ships', 'Seized', 'South Korea', 'GPE', 'Linked', 'Alleged', 'Chinese', 'AND', 'Russian', 'Transactions']]", 'category': 'closed_qa'}
{'input': 'FRANKFURT (Reuters) - HeidelbergCement ( HEIG.DE ) expects the U.S. tax reform to have a negative effect of around 200 million euros ($241 million) on its balance sheet for 2017, the German cement maker said on Tuesday but affirmed its guidance for underlying profits..The revaluation of deferred tax assets is a one-time effect that is not cash-effective and has no impact on earnings before tax or cash flow in 2017, it said, sticking with its guidance for a significant increase in full-year underlying profit..It also said that it expected the lower corporate tax rate in the United States to have a positive effect on annual group net profit and cash flow from 2019..Reporting by Maria Sheahan; Editing by Georgina Prodhan. ', 'output': "[['HeidelbergCement', 'COMP', 'Expect', '200 Million Euros Negative Effect', 'ECON_INDICATOR'], ['HeidelbergCement', 'COMP', 'Operate_In', 'Germany', 'GPE'], ['HeidelbergCement', 'COMP', 'Announce', 'Positive Effect on Annual Group Net Profit', 'ECON_INDICATOR'], ['HeidelbergCement', 'COMP', 'Announce', 'Positive Effect on Cash Flow', 'ECON_INDICATOR'], ['U.S. Tax Reform', 'ORG/GOV', 'Relate_To', '200 Million Euros Negative Effect', 'ECON_INDICATOR'], ['U.S. Tax Reform', 'ORG/GOV', 'Relate_To', 'Positive Effect on Annual Group Net Profit', 'ECON_INDICATOR'], ['U.S. Tax Reform', 'ORG/GOV', 'Relate_To', 'Positive Effect on Cash Flow', 'ECON_INDICATOR']]", 'category': 'closed_qa'}
{'input': 'US blocks MoneyGram sale to Alibabas Ant Financial 1 Hour Ago The Squawk on the Street crew weigh in on the federal regulators objecting to Ant Financials plans to buy MoneyGram due to possible national security risks.', 'output': "[['US', 'GPE', 'Control', 'Federal Regulators', 'ORG/GOV'], ['Federal Regulators', 'ORG/GOV', 'Object', 'Ant Financials', 'ORG', 'Plan', 'Buy', 'MoneyGram', 'ORG'], ['Ant Financials', 'ORG', 'Relate_To', 'Alibaba', 'ORG'], ['Plan', 'CONCEPT', 'Negative_Impact_On', 'National Security', 'CONCEPT'], ['MoneyGram', 'ORG', 'Be_Bought', 'Ant Financials', 'ORG']]", 'category': 'closed_qa'}
{'input': 'SAO PAULO (Reuters) - China’s ride-hailing application Didi Chuxing has agreed to acquire a majority stake in Brazilian app 99, newspaper Valor Economico said on Wednesday, citing sources familiar with the talks..FILE PHOTO: A woman works at the reception of ride-hailing company Didi Chuxing at its headquarters in Beijing, China, May 18, 2016. REUTERS/Kim Kyung-Hoon/File Photo According to the paper, Didi valued 99 at $1 billion, and acquired stakes owned by current shareholders Riverwood Capital, Monashees Inc., Qualcomm Ventures, Tiger Global Management LLC and Softbank Group Corp..Contacted by Reuters, 99 declined to comment and said it will issue a statement “at an appropriate time”..Buyout firms Riverwood and Monashees did not immediately respond to requests for comment. Calls to Tiger Global were not picked up outside business hours..The paper said a $100 million investment announced by Didi in 99 a year ago gave the Chinese company a minority stake in the app..The acquisition intensifies Didi’s global rivalry with Uber, especially in Latin America. Reuters reported on Dec. 7 that Didi plans to enter Mexico this year..The company has made no secret of its desire to expand beyond China, particularly in light of the growing number of Chinese customers who travel overseas. In April, Didi raised $5.5 billion from investors, in part to fund global expansion..Reporting by Tatiana Bautzer, Gabriela Mello and Gram Slattery; Editing by Adrian Croft. ', 'output': "[['Didi Chuxing', 'COMP', 'Acquire', '99', 'COMP'], ['99', 'COMP', 'Has', 'Brazilian app', 'GPE'], ['Didi Chuxing', 'COMP', 'Operate_In', 'China', 'GPE'], ['99', 'COMP', 'Control', 'stakes', 'ORG'], ['Riverwood Capital', 'ORG', 'Control', 'stakes', 'ORG'], ['Monashees Inc.', 'ORG', 'Control', 'stakes', 'ORG'], ['Qualcomm Ventures', 'ORG', 'Control', 'stakes', 'ORG'], ['Tiger Global Management LLC', 'ORG', 'Control', 'stakes', 'ORG'], ['Softbank Group Corp.', 'ORG', 'Control', 'stakes', 'ORG'], ['Didi Chuxing', 'COMP', 'Impact', 'Uber', 'COMP'], ['Didi Chuxing', 'COMP', 'Intend_To', 'Enter', 'Mexico', 'GPE'], ['Didi Chuxing', 'COMP', 'Raise', '$5.5 billion', 'ECON_INDICATOR'], ['Didi Chuxing', 'COMP', 'Operate_In', 'Latin America', 'GPE']]", 'category': 'closed_qa'}
{'input': '1 Hour Ago | 02:32 .Federal Reserve officials expect reductions in corporate and personal taxes to boost consumer and business spending, though they remain unsure of the impact of the new tax law, according to minutes released Wednesday from their December meeting. .Members of the Federal Open Market Committee increased their expectations for 2018 GDP growth from 2.1 percent, or about trend since the post-financial crisis recovery, to 2.5 percent. .Most participants indicated that prospective changes in federal tax policy were a factor that led them to boost their projections of real GDP growth over the next couple of years, the minutes stated. .The FOMC is the Feds monetary policymaking arm. The committee at the meeting voted to increase its benchmark interest rate a quarter point to 1.25 percent to 1.5 percent. The rate is tied to most consumer credit rates. .Much of the discussion as reflected in the minutes show strong observations on the economy. The meeting summary points to significant improvements in payrolls as the unemployment rate dipped to 4.1 percent, and noted that industrial production increased briskly. .Holiday spending was strong in several Fed districts, as many participants expected the proposed cuts in personal taxes to provide some boost to consumer spending. In addition, officials observed that stock market prices improved as well, part of a year in which the S&P 500 rose about 20 percent. .At least some of the credit, particularly for the market gains, went to anticipation of the Republican tax overhaul. Congress had not yet passed the measure when the FOMC met Dec. 12-13. The plan, now law, slashes the corporate tax rate from 35 percent to 21 percent and lowered income tax brackets for most payers. show chapters 9:26 AM ET Tue, 2 Jan 2018 | 03:53 .Broad equity price indexes rose over the intermeeting period, likely reflecting in part investors perceptions of increased odds for the passage of federal tax legislation and an associated potential boost to corporate earnings, the minutes stated. .Looking at conditions more broadly, the document said: Real economic activity appeared to be growing at a solid pace, buttressed by gains in consumer and business spending, supportive financial conditions, and an improving global economy. .However, the minutes on multiple occasions noted that officials remained unsure over just how much a boost in activity would come from the tax plan. For instance, members were quite uncertain about the impact the tax cuts would have on labor supply. .There also was concern, as relayed from business contacts, that the windfall corporations would get from tax cuts would be spent on dividends and share buybacks. .Officials also remained somewhat at loggerheads when it came to inflation. The Fed has consistently missed its 2 percent target for price rises, and members discussed at length the reasons why the reading has remained so low. .Fed officials collectively see inflation likely to meet the target over the medium term, but two members — Neel Kashkari and Charles Evans — voted against the rate hike because theyd like to see more progress on the target. .Most officials judged that much of the softness in core inflation this year reflected transitory factors and that inflation would begin to rise as the influence of these factors waned. However, there was some concern that inflation might stay below the objective for longer than they currently expected. .On other matters, committee members also were largely dismissive about concerns over the yield curve, or the difference in bond yields across various maturities. While an inverted curve — when short-term rates are higher than longer-term rates — often signals a recession, Fed officials said other factors were likely at play that are less ominous. .They generally agreed that the current degree of flatness of the yield curve was not unusual by historical standards. However, several participants thought that it would be important to continue to monitor the slope of the yield curve, the minutes said. .There again were some concerns about market valuations. .While generally looking favorably on the rising stock market indexes, some officials have expressed concern that keeping policy overly accommodative could inflate bubbles. .In light of elevated asset valuations and low financial market volatility, a couple of participants expressed concern that the persistence of highly accommodative financial conditions could, over time, pose risks to financial stability, the minutes said. WATCH: Fed minutes reveal back and forth show chapters ', 'output': "[['Federal Reserve', 'ORG/REG', 'Expect', 'Reductions in Corporate and Personal Taxes', 'CONCEPT'], ['Federal Reserve', 'ORG/REG', 'Unsure', 'Impact of New Tax Law', 'CONCEPT'], ['Federal Open Market Committee', 'ORG/REG', 'Increase', 'Expectations for 2018 GDP Growth', 'ECON_INDICATOR'], ['Federal Open Market Committee', 'ORG/REG', 'Vote', 'Increase Benchmark Interest Rate', 'CONCEPT'], ['Federal Reserve', 'ORG/REG', 'Operate_In', 'Monetary Policymaking Arm', 'ORG/REG'], ['Republican Tax Overhaul', 'CONCEPT', 'Slash', 'Corporate Tax Rate', 'ECON_INDICATOR'], ['Republican Tax Overhaul', 'CONCEPT', 'Lower', 'Income Tax Brackets', 'CONCEPT'], ['Federal Reserve', 'ORG/REG', 'Reflect', 'Investors Perceptions', 'CONCEPT'], ['Federal Reserve', 'ORG/REG', 'Observe', 'Significant Improvements in Payrolls', 'CONCEPT'], ['Federal Reserve', 'ORG/REG', 'Note', 'Unemployment Rate Dipped', 'CONCEPT'], ['Federal Reserve', 'ORG/REG', 'Observe', 'Industrial Production Increased', 'CONCEPT'], ['Federal Reserve', 'ORG/REG', 'Expect', 'Proposed Cuts in Personal Taxes to Provide Boost to Consumer Spending', 'CONCEPT'], ['Fed Officials', 'ORG/REG', 'Observe', 'Stock Market Prices Improved', 'CONCEPT'], ['Fed Officials', 'ORG/REG', 'Anticipate', 'Republican Tax Overhaul', 'CONCEPT'], ['Broad Equity Price Indexes', 'PRODUCT', 'Rise', 'Over Intermeeting Period', 'TIME'], ['Investors', 'PERSON', 'Perceive', 'Increased Odds for Passage of Federal Tax Legislation', 'CONCEPT'], ['Federal Reserve', 'ORG/REG', 'Observe', 'Real Economic Activity Growing at Solid Pace', 'CONCEPT'], ['Federal Reserve', 'ORG/REG', 'Observe', 'Gains in Consumer and Business Spending', 'CONCEPT'], ['Federal Reserve', 'ORG/REG', 'Observe', 'Supportive Financial Conditions', 'CONCEPT'], ['Federal Reserve', 'ORG/REG', 'Observe', 'Improving Global Economy', 'CONCEPT'], ['Federal Reserve', 'ORG/REG', 'Unsure', 'How Much Boost in Activity Would Come from Tax Plan', 'CONCEPT'], ['Federal Reserve', 'ORG/REG', 'Discuss', 'Reasons Why Inflation Has Remained Low', 'CONCEPT'], ['Fed Officials', 'ORG/REG', 'See', 'Inflation Likely to Meet Target Over Medium Term', 'CONCEPT'], ['Neel Kashkari', 'PERSON', 'Vote', 'Against Rate Hike', 'CONCEPT'], ['Charles Evans', 'PERSON', 'Vote', 'Against Rate Hike', 'CONCEPT'], ['Most Officials', 'ORG/REG', 'Judge', 'Much of the Softness in Core Inflation This Year Reflected Transitory Factors', 'CONCEPT'], ['Federal Reserve', 'ORG/REG', 'Monitor', 'Slope of Yield Curve', 'CONCEPT'], ['Federal Reserve', 'ORG/REG', 'Dismissive', 'Concerns Over Yield Curve', 'CONCEPT'], ['Federal Reserve', 'ORG/REG', 'Express', 'Concern Over Elevated Asset Valuations', 'CONCEPT'], ['Federal Reserve', 'ORG/REG', 'Express', 'Concern Over Low Financial Market Volatility', 'CONCEPT'], ['Federal Reserve', 'ORG/REG', 'Concerned', 'Persistence of Highly Accommodative Financial Conditions Could Inflate Bubbles', 'CONCEPT']]", 'category': 'closed_qa'}
{'input': 'Pakistan moves in on alleged terror mastermind Tuesday, January 02, 2018 - 01:05 .Pakistans government is reportedly trying to take down Islamist leader Hafiz Saeed by seizing his charities. The US says the organisations are a terrorist front for the group blamed for the Mumbai attacks. Joel Labi reports.   .Pakistans government is reportedly trying to take down Islamist leader Hafiz Saeed by seizing his charities. The US says the organisations are a terrorist front for the group blamed for the Mumbai attacks. Joel Labi reports.  //reut.rs/2CpnLxn', 'output': "[['Pakistan', 'GPE', 'Participates_In', 'Take_Down', 'ORG'], ['Pakistan', 'GPE', 'Operate_In', 'Government Bodies', 'ORG/GOV'], ['Hafiz Saeed', 'PERSON', 'Is_Member_Of', 'Islamist Leader', 'CONCEPT'], ['Hafiz Saeed', 'PERSON', 'Relate_To', 'Charities', 'ORG'], ['Charities', 'ORG', 'Control', 'Terrorist Front', 'CONCEPT'], ['Terrorist Front', 'CONCEPT', 'Relate_To', 'Mumbai Attacks', 'EVENT'], ['US', 'GPE', 'Say', 'Organizations_Are', 'Terrorist Front', 'CONCEPT'], ['US', 'GPE', 'Relate_To', 'Group_Blamed_For', 'Mumbai Attacks', 'EVENT'], ['Joel Labi', 'PERSON', 'Report', 'Pakistan_Government_Actions', 'ORG/GOV']]", 'category': 'closed_qa'}
{'input': ' 12 PM / Updated 10 minutes ago BRIEF-Andeavor Agreed to Acquire 100% of Equity of Rangeland Energy II LLC Reuters Staff .* REG-ANDEAVOR FURTHER ENHANCES PERMIAN BASIN POSITION THROUGH ACQUISITION OF RANGELAND ENERGY II, LLC .* ANDEAVOR - AGREED TO ACQUIRE 100% OF EQUITY OF RANGELAND ENERGY II LLC .* ANDEAVOR - PLANS TO INTEGRATE ACQUIRED 110-MILE CRUDE OIL PIPELINE, CRUDE OIL STORAGE TERMINALS WITH NEARBY CONAN CRUDE OIL GATHERING SYSTEM Source text for Eikon:  ', 'output': "[['Andeavor', 'COMP', 'Agree', 'Acquire', 'ORG'], ['Andeavor', 'COMP', 'Operate_In', 'Permian Basin', 'GPE'], ['Rangeland Energy II LLC', 'ORG', 'Acquire', 'Andeavor', 'COMP'], ['Rangeland Energy II LLC', 'ORG', 'Integrate', '110-mile Crude Oil Pipeline', 'COMP'], ['Rangeland Energy II LLC', 'ORG', 'Integrate', 'Crude Oil Storage Terminals', 'COMP'], ['Rangeland Energy II LLC', 'ORG', 'Relate_To', 'Conan Crude Oil Gathering System', 'COMP']]", 'category': 'closed_qa'}
{'input': 'January 2, 2018 / 3:04 AM / Updated 7 hours ago German parties at odds ahead of coalition talks Andrea Shalal 5 Min Read .BERLIN (Reuters) - Chancellor Angela Merkel’s conservatives and Social Democrats (SPD) traded barbs about migration and tax cuts on Tuesday amid mounting questions about whether they can agree to renew the “grand coalition” that ruled Germany for the past four years. Acting German Chancellor Angela Merkel address a news conference at the Christian Democratic Union (CDU) party headquarters in Berlin, Germany, December 18, 2017. REUTERS/Hannibal Hanschke .Merkel, under pressure after failing to form a government three months after national elections, hopes to secure a fourth term in office by persuading the centre-left SPD to join the government despite punishing losses in September’s election. .Party leaders will meet for preliminary talks on Jan. 3 ahead of exploratory talks scheduled for Jan. 7 through Jan. 12, but a growing number of politicians now say Merkel might have to rule with a minority government, or face new elections. .SPD deputy leader Thorsten Schaefer-Guembel said recent comments by some conservatives were “counterproductive for every form of government formation” and said they had sparked doubts about the will of conservatives to govern together. .He said a deal on a new coalition was far from certain and it was unclear if the talks could develop sufficient trust. .“A minority government remains an option, even if Chancellor Angela Merkel doesn’t want to acknowledge that,” he said in an interview published Tuesday in the Passauer Neue Presse newspaper. .Schaefer-Guembel cited differences with conservatives on a range of issues and rejected as “absurd” proposals by some conservatives to cut taxes for high-income earners. .Conservatives and the SPD are also at odds over healthcare, immigration, Europe, work regulations and pensions. .Schaefer-Guembel said he backed calls by SPD parliamentary leader Andrea Nahles to raise taxes for the wealthiest and urge fresh efforts to prevent big companies from evading taxes. .Merkel’s Bavarian sister party, the CSU, has distanced itself from the SPD through policy papers calling for corporate tax cuts, reductions in benefits for asylum seekers, higher military spending and limits on immigration. .The powerful economic council of Merkel’s Christian Democrats (CDU) said it will urge CSU party leaders to push for a minority government when they meet this week, arguing that Germany would face “enormous financial burdens for generations” if the SPD pushed through its spending plans in a coalition. .“A grand coalition will be more expensive in the long term than a minority government,” Wolfgang Steiger, secretary general of the council told the Augsburger Allgemeine newspaper. .The SPD initially wanted to stay in opposition, but agreed to explore the possibility of governing with the conservatives in the interest of political stability after Merkel’s coalition talks with two smaller parties collapsed in November. .Experts say new elections could hand more gains to the far-right Alternative for Germany (AfD) party that entered parliament for the first time in September. Merkel says a new coalition would be more stable than minority government. .Bavarian Interior Minister Joachim Herrmann, a CSU negotiator, told the Funke media group his party would insist on limiting immigration levels. It wanted to extend a temporary ban on family reunifications for migrants who were granted “subsidiary protection”, an asylum status for those not officially classed as refugees. .He said his party viewed it as a democratic responsibility to negotiate a new coalition if policy gaps could be overcome. .“I hope the Social Democrats feel the same sense of responsibility,” he said. “We have an urgent need for action on the legislative front.... We urgently need clear majorities in parliament, we need reliable coalitions.” .A top member of the pro-business Free Democrats, which dropped out of coalition talks with conservatives and Greens in November, said such a coalition remained a future possibility. .Alexander Lambsdorff, deputy leader of the FDP’s parliamentary group, also told the Heilbronner Stimme newspaper that he did not exclude the possibility of new elections or a minority government. “That would not be nice, but it also would not result in a constitutional crisis,” he said. Reporting by Andrea Shalal; Editing by Peter Graff', 'output': "[['Angela Merkel', 'PERSON', 'Hope', 'Coalition', 'ORG/GOV'], ['Angela Merkel', 'PERSON', 'Operate_In', 'Germany', 'GPE'], ['Social Democrats', 'ORG', 'Possible_Member_Of', 'Coalition', 'ORG/GOV'], ['Conservatives', 'ORG', 'Possible_Member_Of', 'Coalition', 'ORG/GOV'], ['Angela Merkel', 'PERSON', 'Leader_Of', 'Conservatives', 'ORG'], ['Angela Merkel', 'PERSON', 'Leader_Of', 'Social Democrats', 'ORG'], ['Conservatives', 'ORG', 'At_Odds_With', 'Social Democrats', 'ORG'], ['Social Democrats', 'ORG', 'Reject', 'Tax_Cuts', 'CONCEPT'], ['Social Democrats', 'ORG', 'Back', 'Tax_Increase', 'CONCEPT'], ['Social Democrats', 'ORG', 'Back', 'Efforts', 'CONCEPT'], ['Conservatives', 'ORG', 'Call_For', 'Corporate_Tax_Cuts', 'CONCEPT'], ['Conservatives', 'ORG', 'Call_For', 'Reductions', 'CONCEPT'], ['Conservatives', 'ORG', 'Call_For', 'Higher_Military_Spending', 'CONCEPT'], ['Conservatives', 'ORG', 'Call_For', 'Limits', 'CONCEPT'], ['CSU', 'ORG', 'Sister_Party_Of', 'CDU', 'ORG'], ['CDU', 'ORG', 'Economic_Council', 'CDU_Economic_Council', 'ORG'], ['CDU_Economic_Council', 'ORG', 'Urge', 'Minority_Government', 'ORG/GOV'], ['CDU_Economic_Council', 'ORG', 'Argue', 'Enormous_Financial_Burdens', 'CONCEPT'], ['SPD', 'ORG', 'Initially_Want_To', 'Stay_In_Opposition', 'CONCEPT'], ['SPD', 'ORG', 'Agree', 'Explore', 'CONCEPT'], ['SPD', 'ORG', 'Interest_Of', 'Political_Stability', 'CONCEPT'], ['Merkel', 'PERSON', 'Say', 'New_Coalition', 'ORG/GOV'], ['Merkel', 'PERSON', 'Say', 'More_Stable', 'CONCEPT'], ['CSU', 'ORG', 'Negotiator', 'Joachim_Herrmann', 'PERSON'], ['CSU', 'ORG', 'Insist', 'Limiting_Immigration_Levels', 'CONCEPT'], ['CSU', 'ORG', 'View', 'Democratic_Responsibility', 'CONCEPT'], ['CSU', 'ORG', 'View', 'Reliable_Coalitions', 'CONCEPT'], ['Social Democrats', 'ORG', 'Sense_Of_Responsibility', 'CSU', 'ORG'], ['Free_Democrats', 'ORG', 'Top_Member', 'Alexander_Lambsdorff', 'PERSON'], ['Free_Democrats', 'ORG', 'Deputy_Leader', 'Alexander_Lambsdorff', 'PERSON'], ['Free_Democrats', 'ORG', 'Exclude', 'Constitutional_Crisis', 'CONCEPT'], ['Free_Democrats', 'ORG', 'Not_Exclude', 'New_Elections', 'CONCEPT'], ['Free_Democrats', 'ORG', 'Not_Exclude', 'Minority_Government', 'ORG/GOV']]", 'category': 'closed_qa'}
{'input': 'BOSTON--(BUSINESS WIRE)-- Plymouth Industrial REIT, Inc. (NYSE American: PLYM) announced that on December 20, 2017 it acquired 440 McLean Boulevard in the Chicago Northwest submarket of Elgin, Illinois for $4.1 million in cash. The acquisition is projected to provide an initial yield of 9.7%..The 75,000-square-foot light manufacturing building is leased to Burndy Engineering, a manufacturer of equipment for the natural gas industry and a subsidiary of NYSE-listed Hubbell Corporation. With this acquisition, Plymouth now owns a total of 22 industrial buildings in the Chicago area totaling approximately 3.7 million square feet..Pendleton White, Jr., President and Chief Investment Officer of Plymouth Industrial REIT, noted, “We continue to grow and diversify our presence in Chicago in strong submarkets. Burndy has a long and successful history at 440 McLean Boulevard. Situated in an infill market and a much-preferred location for tenants with one of the best manufacturing labor forces in the greater Chicago area, this building is a great fit for our strategic expansion in Chicago.”.About Plymouth.Plymouth Industrial REIT, Inc. is a full service real estate investment company structured as a vertically integrated, self-administered and self-managed real estate investment trust focused on the acquisition, ownership and management of single and multi-tenant industrial properties, including distribution centers, warehouses and light industrial properties, primarily located in secondary and select primary markets across the United States. The Company seeks to acquire properties that provide current operating income with the opportunity to enhance shareholder value through property re-positioning, capital improvements and restructuring tenant leases..Forward-Looking Statements.This press release includes “ ” that are made pursuant to the safe harbor provisions of Section 27A of the Securities Act of 1933 and of Section 21E of the Securities Exchange Act of 1934. The in this release do not constitute guarantees of future performance. Investors are cautioned that statements in this press release, which are not strictly historical statements, including, without limitation, statements regarding managements plans, objectives and strategies, constitute . Such subject to a number of known and unknown risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results to differ materially from those anticipated by the forward-looking statement, many of which may be beyond our control. Forward-looking statements generally can be identified by the use of forward-looking terminology such as “may,” “plan,” “seek,” “will,” “expect,” “intend,” “estimate,” “anticipate,” “believe” or “continue” or the negative thereof or variations thereon or similar terminology. Any forward-looking information presented herein is made only as of the date of this press release, and we do not undertake any obligation to update or revise any forward-looking information to reflect changes in assumptions, the occurrence of unanticipated events, or otherwise..View source version on businesswire.com : http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20180104005036/en/.SCR Partners.Tripp Sullivan, 615-760-1104.TSullivan@scr-ir.com.Source: Plymouth Industrial REIT, Inc.', 'output': "[['Plymouth Industrial REIT', 'ORG', 'Announce', 'Acquire', 'ORG'], ['Plymouth Industrial REIT', 'ORG', 'Operate_In', 'Chicago Area', 'GPE'], ['440 McLean Boulevard', 'ORG', 'Leased_To', 'Burndy Engineering', 'ORG'], ['Burndy Engineering', 'ORG', 'Subsidiary_Of', 'Hubbell Corporation', 'ORG'], ['Plymouth Industrial REIT', 'ORG', 'Control', '22 industrial buildings', 'CNT'], ['22 industrial buildings', 'CNT', 'Part_Of', 'Chicago Area', 'GPE'], ['Plymouth Industrial REIT', 'ORG', 'Has', '3.7 million square feet', 'ECON_INDICATOR'], ['Plymouth Industrial REIT', 'ORG', 'Introduce', '9.7%', 'ECON_INDICATOR']]", 'category': 'closed_qa'}
{'input': 'WILMINGTON, Del.--(BUSINESS WIRE)-- Andrews & Springer LLC , a boutique securities class action law firm focused on representing shareholders nationwide, is investigating potential breach of fiduciary duty claims against ModusLink Global Solutions, Inc. (NASDAQGS: MLNK) (“ModusLink Global” or the “Company”)..If you currently own shares of ModusLink Global and want to receive additional information and protect your investments free of charge, please visit us at http://www.andrewsspringer.com/cases-investigations/moduslink-global-solutions-class-action-investigation/ or contact Craig J. Springer, Esq. at cspringer@andrewsspringer.com , or call toll free at 1-800-423-6013. You may also follow us on LinkedIn – www.linkedin.com/company/andrews-&-springer-llc , Twitter – www.twitter.com/AndrewsSpringer or Facebook - www.facebook.com/AndrewsSpringer for future updates..Andrews & Springer is a boutique securities class action law firm representing shareholders nationwide who are victims of securities fraud, breaches of fiduciary duty or corporate misconduct. Having formerly defended some of the largest financial institutions in the world, our founding members use their valuable knowledge, experience, and superior skill for the sole purpose of achieving positive results for investors. These traits are the hallmarks of our innovative approach to each case our Firm decides to prosecute. For more information please visit our website at www.andrewsspringer.com . This notice may constitute Attorney Advertising..View source version on businesswire.com : http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20180102005132/en/.Andrews & Springer LLC.Craig J. Springer, Esq., 1-800-423-6013.cspringer@andrewsspringer.com.Source: Andrews & Springer LLC', 'output': "[['Andrews & Springer LLC', 'ORG', 'Investigate', 'ModusLink Global Solutions', 'ORG'], ['ModusLink Global Solutions', 'ORG', 'Potential', 'Breach of Fiduciary Duty', 'CONCEPT'], ['ModusLink Global Solutions', 'ORG', 'Operate_In', 'NASDAQGS', 'FIN_INSTRUMENT'], ['Craig J. Springer', 'PERSON', 'Contact', 'Investors', 'GPE'], ['Craig J. Springer', 'PERSON', 'Works_At', 'Andrews & Springer LLC', 'ORG'], ['Andrews & Springer LLC', 'ORG', 'Has_Website', 'andrewsspringer.com', 'WEBSITE'], ['Andrews & Springer LLC', 'ORG', 'Use_Social_Media', 'LinkedIn', 'ORG'], ['Andrews & Springer LLC', 'ORG', 'Use_Social_Media', 'Twitter', 'ORG'], ['Andrews & Springer LLC', 'ORG', 'Use_Social_Media', 'Facebook', 'ORG']]", 'category': 'closed_qa'}
{'input': 'The story of college football in the playoff era can be told in three words: “We Want Bama.”.For at least the last four years, fans of every other team celebrated their biggest wins and described their wildest ambitions by putting themselves in the same breath as Alabama. The sport’s haughtiest honor has become proclaiming your team good enough to step on the same field as the Crimson Tide. Some were earnest. Some were ironic. But almost everyone who wanted Bama—and got Bama—regretted it afterward..... ', 'output': "[['College Football', 'SECTOR', 'Relate_To', 'Playoff Era', 'EVENT'], ['Fans', 'PERSON', 'Celebrate', 'Biggest Wins', 'CONCEPT'], ['Fans', 'PERSON', 'Describe', 'Wildest Ambitions', 'CONCEPT'], ['Fans', 'PERSON', 'Put', 'Themselves', 'PERSON'], ['Fans', 'PERSON', 'Proclaim', 'Their Team', 'COMP'], ['Their Team', 'COMP', 'Good Enough', 'CONCEPT'], ['Their Team', 'COMP', 'Step On', 'Same Field', 'SECTOR'], ['Almost Everyone', 'PERSON', 'Who', 'Wanted Bama', 'COMP'], ['Almost Everyone', 'PERSON', 'Who', 'Got Bama', 'COMP'], ['Almost Everyone', 'PERSON', 'Regretted', 'It', 'CONCEPT']]", 'category': 'closed_qa'}
{'input': 'HAMILTON, Bermuda--(BUSINESS WIRE)-- Aspen Insurance Holdings Limited (“Aspen”) (NYSE:AHL) will release its fourth quarter 2017 financial results on Wednesday, February 7, 2018 following the close of the New York Stock Exchange. A conference call to discuss Aspen’s results will follow at 8:00am (ET) on Thursday, February 8, 2018..To participate in the conference call on February 8 by phone:.Please call to register at least 10 minutes before the conference call begins, dialling:.+1 (844) 378 6481 (U.S. toll free).+1 (412) 542 4176 (international).Conference ID: 10114711.To listen live online:.Aspen will provide a live webcast on the Aspen website ..To download the materials:.The earnings press release and a detailed financial supplement will also be published on the Aspen website ..To listen later:.A replay of the call will be available approximately two hours after the end of the live call for 14 days via phone. To listen to the replay by phone please dial:.+1 (877) 344 7529 (U.S. toll free).+1 (412) 317 0088 (international).Replay Access Code: 10114711.The webcast replay will be also available at www.aspen.co.NOTES TO EDITORS :.About Aspen Insurance Holdings Limited.Aspen provides reinsurance and insurance coverage to clients in various domestic and global markets through wholly-owned subsidiaries and offices in Australia, Bermuda, Canada, France, Germany, Ireland, Singapore, Switzerland, the United Arab Emirates, the United Kingdom and the United States. For the year ended December 31, 2016, Aspen reported $12.1 billion in total assets, $5.3 billion in gross reserves, $3.6 billion in total shareholders’ equity and $3.1 billion in gross written premiums. Its operating subsidiaries have been assigned a rating of “A” by Standard & Poor’s Financial Services LLC (“S&P”), an “A” (“Excellent”) by A.M. Best Company Inc. (“A.M. Best”) and an “A2” by Moody’s Investors Service, Inc. (“Moody’s”)..For further information.Please visit www.aspen.co ..View source version on businesswire.com : http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20180103005586/en/.Investors.Mark Jones, +1 646-289-4945.Senior Vice President, Investor Relations, Aspen.mark.p.jones@aspen.co.or.Media.Steve Colton, +44 20 7184 8337.Head of Group Communications, Aspen.steve.colton@aspen.co.Source: Aspen Insurance Holdings Limited', 'output': "[['Aspen Insurance Holdings Limited', 'ORG', 'Release', 'fourth quarter 2017 financial results', 'ECON_INDICATOR'], ['Aspen Insurance Holdings Limited', 'ORG', 'Operate_In', 'New York Stock Exchange', 'GPE'], ['Aspen Insurance Holdings Limited', 'ORG', 'Conference_Call', 'Thursday, February 8, 2018', 'EVENT'], ['Aspen Insurance Holdings Limited', 'ORG', 'Phone', '+1 (844) 378 6481', 'FIN_INSTRUMENT'], ['Aspen Insurance Holdings Limited', 'ORG', 'Phone', '+1 (412) 542 4176', 'FIN_INSTRUMENT'], ['Aspen Insurance Holdings Limited', 'ORG', 'Conference ID', '10114711', 'ECON_INDICATOR'], ['Aspen Insurance Holdings Limited', 'ORG', 'Webcast', 'Aspen website', 'PRODUCT'], ['Aspen Insurance Holdings Limited', 'ORG', 'Publish', 'earnings press release', 'PRODUCT'], ['Aspen Insurance Holdings Limited', 'ORG', 'Publish', 'detailed financial supplement', 'PRODUCT'], ['Aspen Insurance Holdings Limited', 'ORG', 'Phone', '+1 (877) 344 7529', 'FIN_INSTRUMENT'], ['Aspen Insurance Holdings Limited', 'ORG', 'Phone', '+1 (412) 317 0088', 'FIN_INSTRUMENT'], ['Aspen Insurance Holdings Limited', 'ORG', 'Replay Access Code', '10114711', 'ECON_INDICATOR'], ['Aspen Insurance Holdings Limited', 'ORG', 'Webcast Replay', 'www.aspen.co', 'GPE'], ['Aspen Insurance Holdings Limited', 'ORG', 'Raise', 'reinsurance and insurance coverage', 'SERVICE'], ['Aspen Insurance Holdings Limited', 'ORG', 'Operate_In', 'various domestic and global markets', 'SECTOR'], ['Aspen Insurance Holdings Limited', 'ORG', 'Assigned', 'rating of “A” by S&P', 'CONCEPT'], ['Aspen Insurance Holdings Limited', 'ORG', 'Assigned', 'rating of “A” (“Excellent”) by A.M. Best', 'CONCEPT'], ['Aspen Insurance Holdings Limited', 'ORG', 'Assigned', 'rating of “A2” by Moody’s', 'CONCEPT'], ['Aspen Insurance Holdings Limited', 'ORG', 'Reported', '$12.1 billion in total assets', 'ECON_INDICATOR'], ['Aspen Insurance Holdings Limited', 'ORG', 'Reported', '$5.3 billion in gross reserves', 'ECON_INDICATOR'], ['Aspen Insurance Holdings Limited', 'ORG', 'Reported', '$3.6 billion in total shareholders’ equity', 'ECON_INDICATOR'], ['Aspen Insurance Holdings Limited', 'ORG', 'Reported', '$3.1 billion in gross written premiums', 'ECON_INDICATOR']]", 'category': 'closed_qa'}
{'input': 'MINNEAPOLIS--(BUSINESS WIRE)-- CNB Investment Trust II (the “Trust”), an indirect, wholly owned subsidiary of Wells Fargo & Company (the “Company”) (NYSE: WFC), submitted today a redemption notice for redemption on February 1, 2018 of all of its Series B Preferred Shares (CUSIP numbers 12615C204, 12615C303), at a redemption price equal to $1,000 stated value per share plus dividends accrued and unpaid for the current dividend period through the redemption date..The redemption agent for the Series B Preferred Shares is Wells Fargo Bank, National Association, 1110 Centre Pointe Curve, Suite 101, Mendota Heights, Minnesota 55120. Payment of the redemption price will be made by the redemption agent for certificated shares, and through the facilities of The Depository Trust Company for book-entry shares..Following the redemption of the Series B Preferred Shares, and subject to the requisite consent of its remaining shareholders, the Trust is expected to dissolve. CNB Investment Trust I, an indirect, wholly owned subsidiary of the Company, is also expected to dissolve..About Wells Fargo.Wells Fargo & Company (NYSE: WFC) is a diversified, community-based financial services company with $1.9 trillion in assets. Wells Fargo’s vision is to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them succeed financially. Founded in 1852 and headquartered in San Francisco, Wells Fargo provides banking, insurance, investments, mortgage, and consumer and commercial finance through more than 8,500 locations, 13,000 ATMs, the internet ( wellsfargo.com ) and mobile banking, and has offices in 42 countries and territories to support customers who conduct business in the global economy. With approximately 271,000 team members, Wells Fargo serves one in three households in the United States. Wells Fargo & Company was ranked No. 25 on Fortune’s 2017 rankings of America’s largest corporations..View source version on businesswire.com : http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20180102005093/en/.Media.Ancel Martinez, 415-222-3858.or.Investors.Tanya Quinn, 415-396-7495.Source: Wells Fargo & Company', 'output': "[['CNB Investment Trust II', 'ORG', 'Submit', 'redemption notice', 'EVENT'], ['CNB Investment Trust II', 'ORG', 'Operate_In', 'Wells Fargo & Company', 'ORG/COMP'], ['Wells Fargo & Company', 'ORG/COMP', 'Has', 'NYSE', 'EXCH'], ['Wells Fargo & Company', 'ORG/COMP', 'Operate_In', 'San Francisco', 'GPE'], ['Series B Preferred Shares', 'FIN_INSTRUMENT', 'Redeem', 'February 1, 2018', 'DATE'], ['Series B Preferred Shares', 'FIN_INSTRUMENT', 'Has', 'CUSIP numbers 12615C204, 12615C303', 'CONCEPT'], ['Wells Fargo Bank', 'ORG/COMP', 'Is_Member_Of', 'Wells Fargo & Company', 'ORG/COMP'], ['Wells Fargo Bank', 'ORG/COMP', 'Is_Member_Of', 'National Association', 'ORG/REG'], ['Wells Fargo Bank', 'ORG/COMP', 'Redemption_Agent', 'Series B Preferred Shares', 'FIN_INSTRUMENT'], ['Redemption agent', 'ORG/COMP', 'Pay', 'redemption price', 'CONCEPT'], ['The Depository Trust Company', 'ORG/COMP', 'Facilitates', 'book-entry shares', 'PRODUCT'], ['Trust', 'ORG', 'Dissolve', 'after redemption', 'EVENT'], ['Trust', 'ORG', 'Subject_To', 'requisite consent of its remaining shareholders', 'CONCEPT'], ['CNB Investment Trust I', 'ORG', 'Expected_To_Dissolve', 'None', 'CONCEPT'], ['Wells Fargo & Company', 'ORG/COMP', 'Has', '1.9 trillion dollars', 'ECON_INDICATOR', 'in assets'], ['Wells Fargo & Company', 'ORG/COMP', 'Vision', 'satisfy customers financial needs', 'CONCEPT'], ['Wells Fargo & Company', 'ORG/COMP', 'Vision', 'help customers succeed financially', 'CONCEPT'], ['Wells Fargo & Company', 'ORG/COMP', 'Founded', '1852', 'DATE'], ['Wells Fargo & Company', 'ORG/COMP', 'Headquartered', 'San Francisco', 'GPE'], ['Wells Fargo & Company', 'ORG/COMP', 'Provides', 'banking, insurance, investments, mortgage, and consumer and commercial finance', 'CONCEPT'], ['Wells Fargo & Company', 'ORG/COMP', 'Provides', 'through more than 8,500 locations, 13,000 ATMs', 'CONCEPT'], ['Wells Fargo & Company', 'ORG/COMP', 'Provides', 'internet and mobile banking', 'CONCEPT'], ['Wells Fargo & Company', 'ORG/COMP', 'Has', 'offices in 42 countries and territories', 'CONCEPT'], ['Wells Fargo & Company', 'ORG/COMP', 'Serves', 'one in three households in the United States', 'CONCEPT'], ['Wells Fargo & Company', 'ORG/COMP', 'Ranked', 'No. 25 on Fortune’s 2017 rankings of America’s largest corporations', 'CONCEPT'], ['Wells Fargo & Company', 'ORG/COMP', 'Has', 'approximately 271,000 team members', 'CONCEPT']]", 'category': 'closed_qa'}
{'input': 'DOW JONES, A NEWS CORP COMPANY News Corp is a network of leading companies in the worlds of diversified media, news, education, and information services. DOW JONES ', 'output': "[['DOW JONES', 'EVENT', 'Operate_In', 'News Corp', 'ORG'], ['News Corp', 'ORG', 'Is_Member_Of', 'Diversified Media Sector', 'SECTOR'], ['News Corp', 'ORG', 'Is_Member_Of', 'News Sector', 'SECTOR'], ['News Corp', 'ORG', 'Is_Member_Of', 'Education Sector', 'SECTOR'], ['News Corp', 'ORG', 'Is_Member_Of', 'Information Services Sector', 'SECTOR']]", 'category': 'closed_qa'}
{'input': 'By Jeff John Roberts 2:03 PM EST .The new year has already brought some surprises on the cryptocurrency front, but the biggest one is about Ripple: In the last 24 hours, the currency has climbed around 25% to break $3 and lock up second place behind bitcoin. .Ripple’s recent run is remarkable in part because it has eclipsed Ethereum, which was long the number two digital currency, and considered to be the only real rival to bitcoin. .Here is a screenshot from Coinmarketcap that shows the new pecking order as of early Wednesday afternoon ET: .As you can see, Ripple now has a market cap of $120 billion—an amount that is nearly 35% higher than Ethereum, and worth nearly half that of bitcoin. It’s unclear what is driving the price surge, though interest from new hedge funds is likely one big reason. .Ripple’s emergence is also notable because, unlike other digital currencies on the list, it is not created by a decentralized mining process. Instead, Ripple’s currency supply—technically known as XRP—was created in one swoop, and a large portion is held by the company itself as a sort of treasury stock. .As CEO Brad Garlinghouse explained to Fortune this summer , Ripple is able to use its XRP supply as a strategic asset while it builds out its business of supplying banks with a blockchain-based source of liquidity. .The reaction to Ripple’s latest rise has been met with some grousing on Twitter by some who suggest it as a gimmick rather than a real digital currency: The “decentralized computer of the future”™ is overtaken by a fidget spinner. pic.twitter.com/kUf4tCgaXU .— Oleg Andreev (@oleganza) January 2, 2018 .Others note, however, that if Garlinghouse achieves Ripple’s goal of disrupting the existing global financial infrastructure, the consequences would be profound: If we suspend disbelief for a second and $XRP actually becomes a global reserve that is used as a bridge currency which disrupts correspondent banking, then Ripple will be the most successful company of all time. .— Ryan Selkis (@twobitidiot) January 3, 2018 And if we come back to the real world, this statement also shows you that the global financial institutions are not going to adopt someone elses bridge currency. If they do, Ripple will have showcased the negotiating prowess of a nation-state. .Thats mind-bending, so unlikely. https://t.co/57XyRwIHv5 .— Ryan Selkis (@twobitidiot) January 3, 2018 .The question on whether Ripple will ultimately be a world-changer, or simply an also-ran novelty, hinges in large part on whether banks adopt XRP as a so-called bridge currency to move money around. .Skeptics say this is unlikely because it is centralized and cannot provide enough liquidity compared to bitcoin. Garlinghouse, however, has argued that Ripple offers a faster and cheaper ledger system, and comes with less risk for banks than bitcoin. .Meanwhile, one obvious beneficiary of Ripple’s surge is co-founder Chris Larsen, who is now one of the richest men in the world (the $37 billion cited below is based on XRP trading at $2.39 so Larsen’s wealth is now even higher): Ripple co-founder Chris Larsen is now worth $37 billion due to his huge holdings of XRP (Ripples coin), making him the 15th richest American: https://t.co/wBNmLd5NrF pic.twitter.com/VYTOu4RQR4 .— Jeff Kauflin (@JeffKauflin) January 2, 2018 .In response to Ripple’s price surge, a company spokesperson provided the following statement: .In a year punctuated by the dramatic rise of digital assets, XRP has out performed the entire sector and looks likely to end the year up more than 45,000%. XRP’s performance is driven by a keen focus on solving a real global payments problem for real customers – and at fractions of a penny and about 3 seconds per transaction – it is cheaper, faster and more efficient than BTC or ETH. As others have pointed out, Bitcoin isn’t going to solve a payments problem when a transaction costs $40 and takes hours to complete. .The market seems to increasingly understand that there’s real utility for XRP in solving a massive cross-border payments and liquidity problem that is measured in the trillions of dollars. .For those interested in purchasing Ripple—to be clear, Fortune does not endorse buying XRP or any other digital currency— here is a guide for how to do so. SPONSORED FINANCIAL CONTENT ', 'output': "[['Jeff John Roberts', 'PERSON', 'Write', 'Ripple', 'ORG'], ['Ripple', 'ORG', 'Climb', '$3', 'ECON_INDICATOR'], ['Ripple', 'ORG', 'Eclipse', 'Ethereum', 'ORG'], ['Ripple', 'ORG', 'Has', 'XRP', 'PRODUCT'], ['XRP', 'PRODUCT', 'Created', 'one swoop', 'NONE'], ['XRP', 'PRODUCT', 'Held', 'Company', 'ORG'], ['Brad Garlinghouse', 'PERSON', 'Explain', 'Ripple', 'ORG'], ['Ripple', 'ORG', 'Use', 'XRP', 'PRODUCT'], ['Ripple', 'ORG', 'Build', 'Business', 'SECTOR'], ['Ripple', 'ORG', 'Supply', 'Banks', 'SECTOR'], ['XRP', 'PRODUCT', 'Bridge Currency', 'NONE'], ['Ripple', 'ORG', 'Disrupt', 'Correspondent Banking', 'NONE'], ['Ripple', 'ORG', 'Most Successful', 'Company', 'SECTOR'], ['Ripple', 'ORG', 'Adopt', 'Global Reserve', 'NONE'], ['Ripple', 'ORG', 'Disrupt', 'Global Financial Infrastructure', 'NONE'], ['Ripple', 'ORG', 'Negotiating Prowess', 'Nation-State', 'GPE'], ['Banks', 'SECTOR', 'Adopt', 'XRP', 'PRODUCT'], ['Skeptics', 'PERSON', 'Say', 'XRP', 'PRODUCT'], ['XRP', 'PRODUCT', 'Centralized', 'NONE'], ['XRP', 'PRODUCT', 'Less Risk', 'Banks', 'SECTOR'], ['Bitcoin', 'PRODUCT', 'Rival', 'XRP', 'PRODUCT'], ['Ripple', 'ORG', 'Faster', 'Ledger System', 'NONE'], ['Ripple', 'ORG', 'Cheaper', 'Banks', 'SECTOR'], ['Chris Larsen', 'PERSON', 'Co-founder', 'Ripple', 'ORG'], ['Chris Larsen', 'PERSON', 'Richest', 'American', 'GPE'], ['XRP', 'PRODUCT', 'Trading', '$2.39', 'ECON_INDICATOR'], ['Company Spokesperson', 'PERSON', 'Provide', 'Statement', 'PRODUCT'], ['XRP', 'PRODUCT', 'Out Perform', 'Sector', 'SECTOR'], ['XRP', 'PRODUCT', 'End Year', '45000%', 'ECON_INDICATOR'], ['XRP', 'PRODUCT', 'Solve', 'Payments Problem', 'NONE'], ['XRP', 'PRODUCT', 'Cheaper', 'BTC', 'PRODUCT'], ['XRP', 'PRODUCT', 'Faster', 'ETH', 'PRODUCT'], ['XRP', 'PRODUCT', 'Efficient', 'BTC', 'PRODUCT'], ['XRP', 'PRODUCT', 'Efficient', 'ETH', 'PRODUCT'], ['Bitcoin', 'PRODUCT', 'Solve', 'Payments Problem', 'NONE'], ['Transaction', 'NONE', 'Cost', '$40', 'ECON_INDICATOR'], ['Transaction', 'NONE', 'Take', 'Hours', 'NONE'], ['XRP', 'PRODUCT', 'Understand', 'Real Utility', 'NONE'], ['XRP', 'PRODUCT', 'Solve', 'Massive Problem', 'NONE'], ['Problem', 'NONE', 'Measured', 'Trillions Dollars', 'ECON_INDICATOR']]", 'category': 'closed_qa'}
{'input': 'The U.S. Navy has a fleetwide deficiency that renders two essential naval operations impossible. Because Americans ships are vulnerable to antiship missiles, Navy doctrine bars them from sailing within 100 miles of a hostile shore. This prevents the Navy from a visible show of force and from mounting an amphibious assault against a well-defended position...Why does the U.S. need these capabilities? Because the main peacetime mission of the Navy is diplomatic and political, and that sometimes requires a show of force in dangerous...  ', 'output': "[['U.S. Navy', 'ORG/GOV', 'Has', 'Fleetwide Deficiency', 'CONCEPT'], ['Americans Ships', 'COMP', 'Relate_To', 'Naval Operations', 'CONCEPT'], ['Naval Operations', 'CONCEPT', 'Impact', 'Visibility', 'CONCEPT'], ['Naval Operations', 'CONCEPT', 'Impact', 'Amphibious Assault', 'CONCEPT'], ['U.S. Navy', 'ORG/GOV', 'Operate_In', 'Naval Operations', 'CONCEPT'], ['U.S.', 'GPE', 'Need', 'Capabilities', 'CONCEPT'], ['Capabilities', 'CONCEPT', 'Relate_To', 'Peacetime Mission', 'CONCEPT'], ['Peacetime Mission', 'CONCEPT', 'Relate_To', 'Diplomacy', 'CONCEPT'], ['Peacetime Mission', 'CONCEPT', 'Relate_To', 'Politics', 'CONCEPT'], ['Peacetime Mission', 'CONCEPT', 'Impact', 'Dangerous Situations', 'CONCEPT']]", 'category': 'closed_qa'}
{'input': 'HOUSTON--(BUSINESS WIRE)-- Helix Energy Solutions Group, Inc. (NYSE: HLX) announced today the appointment of Geoffrey (Geoff) Wagner as Executive Vice President and Chief Commercial Officer..Mr. Wagner has more than 15 years of experience in the energy industry. Prior to joining Helix, Mr. Wagner spent several years in executive leadership with Atwood Oceanics, a global provider of offshore drilling services, serving as Vice President of Strategic Planning, Vice President of Technical Services and Supply Chain and Vice President of Marketing and Business Development. Mr. Wagner joined Atwood from Transocean, where he spent five years in various management positions with increasing responsibility, and prior to that, he worked with SeaRiver Maritime, a subsidiary of ExxonMobil. Mr. Wagner holds an MBA from the Jones Graduate School of Business at Rice University and an undergraduate degree in Marine Engineering and Nautical Science from the United States Merchant Marine Academy at Kings Point, New York..In connection with Mr. Wagner’s appointment, Owen Kratz, Chief Executive Officer of Helix, stated, We are excited to have Geoff join Helix. He complements our executive leadership team, and we believe his experience and drive makes him the right choice to lead our company’s commercial strategy. We also expect to benefit as a company from Geoff’s past experience in operational execution and process development..About Helix.Helix Energy Solutions Group, Inc., headquartered in Houston, Texas, is an international offshore energy services company that provides specialty services to the offshore energy industry, with a focus on well intervention and robotics operations. For more information about Helix, please visit our website at www.HelixESG.com ..Forward-Looking Statements.This press release contains forward-looking statements that involve risks, uncertainties and assumptions that could cause our results to differ materially from those expressed or implied by such forward-looking statements. All statements, other than statements of historical fact, are forward-looking statements within the meaning of the Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995, including, without limitation, any statements regarding our strategy; any statements regarding visibility and future utilization; any projections of financial items; any statements regarding future operations expenditures; any statements regarding the plans, strategies and objectives of management for future operations; any statements concerning developments; any statements regarding future economic conditions or performance; any statements of expectation or belief; and any statements of assumptions underlying any of the foregoing. The forward-looking statements are subject to a number of known and unknown risks, uncertainties and other factors including but not limited to the performance of contracts by suppliers, customers and partners; actions by governmental and regulatory authorities; operating hazards and delays; our ultimate ability to realize current backlog; employee management issues; complexities of global political and economic developments; geologic risks; volatility of oil and gas prices and other risks described from time to time in our reports filed with the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), including the Companys most recently filed Annual Report on Form 10-K and in the Company’s other filings with the SEC, which are available free of charge on the SEC’s website at www.sec.gov . We assume no obligation and do not intend to update these forward-looking statements except as required by the securities laws..Social Media.From time to time we provide information about Helix on Twitter ( @Helix_ESG ) and LinkedIn ( www.linkedin.com/company/helix-energy-solutions-group )..About Helix.Helix Energy Solutions Group, Inc., headquartered in Houston, Texas, is an international offshore energy services company that provides specialty services to the offshore energy industry, with a focus on well intervention and robotics operations. For more information about Helix, please visit our website at www.HelixESG.com ..View source version on businesswire.com : http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20180102005905/en/.Helix Energy Solutions Group, Inc..Erik Staffeldt, 281-618-0400.Senior Vice President & CFO.Source: Helix Energy Solutions Group, Inc.', 'output': "[['Helix Energy Solutions Group', 'ORG', 'Announce', 'Appointment of Geoffrey Wagner', 'PERSON'], ['Geoffrey Wagner', 'PERSON', 'Has', 'More than 15 years of experience in the energy industry', 'CONCEPT'], ['Geoffrey Wagner', 'PERSON', 'Operate_In', 'Atwood Oceanics', 'ORG'], ['Atwood Oceanics', 'ORG', 'Control', 'Global provider of offshore drilling services', 'SECTOR'], ['Geoffrey Wagner', 'PERSON', 'Participates_In', 'Executive leadership with Atwood Oceanics', 'ORG'], ['Geoffrey Wagner', 'PERSON', 'Join', 'Transocean', 'ORG'], ['Geoffrey Wagner', 'PERSON', 'Work', 'SeaRiver Maritime', 'ORG'], ['Geoffrey Wagner', 'PERSON', 'Hold', 'MBA from the Jones Graduate School of Business at Rice University', 'EDUCATION'], ['Geoffrey Wagner', 'PERSON', 'Hold', 'Undergraduate degree in Marine Engineering and Nautical Science from the United States Merchant Marine Academy at Kings Point, New York', 'EDUCATION'], ['Helix Energy Solutions Group', 'ORG', 'Impact', 'Company’s commercial strategy', 'CONCEPT'], ['Helix Energy Solutions Group', 'ORG', 'Operate_In', 'Houston, Texas', 'GPE'], ['Helix Energy Solutions Group', 'ORG', 'Provide', 'Specialty services to the offshore energy industry', 'SECTOR'], ['Helix Energy Solutions Group', 'ORG', 'Focus', 'Well intervention and robotics operations', 'SECTOR']]", 'category': 'closed_qa'}
{'input': 'Silicon Valley smart guy bets big on bitcoin 4:13am IST - 01:13 .** OTC-traded Bitcoin Investment Trust GBTC.PK up 13.5 pct at $2387.70 after WSJ reported Peter Thiels Founders Fund amassed hundreds of millions of dollars worth bitcoins (http://on.wsj.com/2EA1mLo)** Founders bought about $15-$20 mln worth bitcoins, now worth hundreds of millions of dollars after bitcoins rally in the past year, according to the WSJ report, citing people familiar with the matter** Bitcoin Investment Trust allows investors to take a bet on the price of bitcoin without complication of buying and safeguarding them directly** Bitcoin rose above $15,000 to trade at $15,017.63 (Full Story)** The crypto-currency has surged more than 15 times in value over the last 12 months on the back of enthusiasm from retail investors and launch of bitcoin futures (Full Story)   .** OTC-traded Bitcoin Investment Trust GBTC.PK up 13.5 pct at $2387.70 after WSJ reported Peter Thiels Founders Fund amassed hundreds of millions of dollars worth bitcoins (http://on.wsj.com/2EA1mLo) ** Founders bought about $15-$20 mln worth bitcoins, now worth hundreds of millions of dollars after bitcoins rally in the past year, according to the WSJ report, citing people familiar with the matter ** Bitcoin Investment Trust allows investors to take a bet on the price of bitcoin without complication of buying and safeguarding them directly ** Bitcoin rose above $15,000 to trade at $15,017.63 (Full Story) ** The crypto-currency has surged more than 15 times in value over the last 12 months on the back of enthusiasm from retail investors and launch of bitcoin futures (Full Story)  //reut.rs/2A87UO0', 'output': "[['Peter Thiel', 'PERSON', 'Invests_In', 'Bitcoin', 'CONCEPT'], ['Founders Fund', 'ORG', 'Control', 'Bitcoins', 'CONCEPT'], ['Bitcoin Investment Trust', 'COMP', 'Relate_To', 'Bitcoin', 'CONCEPT'], ['Investors', 'PERSON', 'Participates_In', 'Bitcoin Investment Trust', 'COMP'], ['Bitcoin', 'CONCEPT', 'Raise', '15000', 'ECON_INDICATOR'], ['Bitcoin', 'CONCEPT', 'Impact', 'Retail Investors Enthusiasm', 'CONCEPT'], ['Bitcoin', 'CONCEPT', 'Impact', 'Bitcoin Futures', 'CONCEPT']]", 'category': 'closed_qa'}
{'input': 'January 4, 2018 / 10:03 AM / Updated 8 minutes ago Continental, Bosch to buy five percent stakes in map firm HERE Reuters Staff 3 Min Read .BERLIN (Reuters) - German automotive suppliers Continental and Bosch are to buy stakes of 5 percent each in digital mapping firm HERE to gain more expertise in driver-assistance and other data-based technologies. FILE PHOTO - Logo of German tyre company Continental is seen before the annual news conference in Hanover, Germany March 2, 2017. REUTERS/Fabian Bimmer .Germany’s three leading premium automakers BMW, Daimler and Volkswagen’s ( VOWG_p.DE ) Audi bought HERE for 2.8 billion euros (£2.49 billion) in 2015 from Finnish telecoms group Nokia to expand investments in autonomous-driving technology. .The three car companies are spending billions of euros on developing electric cars and software-based mobility services as tougher emission rules and connectivity are transforming the auto industry. .Continental said on Thursday it would sign a collaboration agreement with the Dutch provider of high-definition maps to pave the way for technologies that provide data for the efficient transportation of people and goods. .Software and electronics products are biggest drivers of growth at Hanover-based Continental which also makes fuel-injection systems and vehicle tyres. It plans to boost total sales to more than 50 billion euros by 2020 from 40.5 billion in 2016. FILE PHOTO - The Bosch logo is reflected in a semiconductor wafer in the company manufacturing base in Reutlingen, Germany, June 16, 2017. REUTERS/Michaela Rehle .Bosch’s statement on Thursday referred to plans by HERE to increase its diversification into non-automotive applications - a move that could help to offset risks surrounding the eventual arrival of fully autonomous cars for the mass market. .“Bosch is more than cars,” Chief Executive Volkmar Denner said in the statement. .He said the company saw synergies with data-based services for smart homes and smart cities - terms broadly describing the use of technology to find efficiencies everywhere from the factory floor to road traffic management. .Chip maker Intel also holds a 15 percent stake in HERE. A group of investors led by Chinese mapping firm Navinfo and internet giant Tencent in September cancelled a previously announced plan to buy 10 percent of HERE, after failing to win U.S. approval. .Both Bosch and Conti said they had agreed not to disclose how much they were paying for their stakes. Reporting by Andreas Cremer; Editing by Maria Sheahan and Jane Merriman', 'output': "[['Continental', 'ORG', 'Buy', '5%', 'ECON_INDICATOR'], ['Bosch', 'ORG', 'Buy', '5%', 'ECON_INDICATOR'], ['Continental', 'ORG', 'Collaboration', 'HERE', 'ORG'], ['Bosch', 'ORG', 'Participates_In', 'Data-based services', 'CONCEPT'], ['Continental', 'ORG', 'Relate_To', 'Smart homes', 'CONCEPT'], ['Continental', 'ORG', 'Relate_To', 'Smart cities', 'CONCEPT'], ['BMW', 'ORG', 'Buy', 'HERE', 'ORG'], ['Daimler', 'ORG', 'Buy', 'HERE', 'ORG'], ['Audi', 'ORG', 'Buy', 'HERE', 'ORG'], ['HERE', 'ORG', 'Control', 'Autonomous-driving technology', 'CONCEPT'], ['HERE', 'ORG', 'Diversification', 'Non-automotive applications', 'CONCEPT'], ['Navinfo', 'ORG', 'Lead', 'Group of investors', 'ORG'], ['Tencent', 'ORG', 'Lead', 'Group of investors', 'ORG'], ['Intel', 'ORG', 'Hold', '15%', 'ECON_INDICATOR'], ['HERE', 'ORG', 'Cancel', 'Plan', 'CONCEPT']]", 'category': 'closed_qa'}
